A Guide to the Minutes of the Virginia Dept. for Professional and Occupational Regulation, 2014-2020.
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Minutes of the Virginia Dept. for Professional and Occupational Regulation,
2011-2020.
The Library of Virginia
2011-2020
Virginia. Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation.
8.35 cu. ft. (9 boxes)
Administrative Information
Arranged by accession.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 51966 was transferred by the Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 17 February 2017
Accession 52208 was transferred by the Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 18 January 2018.
Accession 53968 was transferred by the Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 13 January 2020.
Accession 53634 was transferred by the Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 24 May 2022.
Historical Information
The Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation was formed in 1948 under the Government Reorganization Act. On March 24, 1978, the agency's name was changed to the Dept. of Commerce. Effective July, 1993, the Department regained its original name. The Department has been responsible for the these Boards: Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects; Board for Asbestos, Lead and Home Inspectors; Aucioneers Board; Board for Barbers and Cosmetology; Boxing, Martial Arts and Wrestling Advisory Board; Board for Branch Pilots; Cemetery Board; Common Interest Community Board; Board for Contractors; Fair Housing Board; Board for Hearing Aid Specialists and Opticians; Polygraph Examiners Advisory Board; Board for Professional Soil Scientists, Wetland Professionals and Geologists; Real Estate Board; Real Estate Appraisers Board; Board for Waste Management Facility Operators; and Board for Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage System Professionals.
The primary function of the Department is to provide administrative support to the boards within the Department which are currently responsible for licensing and certification of occupations. The Boards have regulatory authority for the issuance, suspension and revocation of certificates, permits, and licenses. The Department is operated by a director who is appointed by the Governor. The Department's activities are broken-down into sub-programs for each of the examining boards. Major activities include review and evaluation of the regulation of professions, examination of those wishing to enter one of the regulated professions, licensing, consumer complaint resolution, and investigation of alleged violations or laws. The mission of the Department of Professional and Occupational Regulation is to protect the health, safety and welfare of Virginians, while promoting a competent workforce, fair housing opportunities, and a productive economy.
Scope and Content
Minutes, 2011-2020, of the Virginia Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation are arranged alphabetically by board name within each accession. This series consists of official minutes of the boards under the auspices of the Dept., with related attachments and agendas. Also may include committee, council, public hearing and section minutes, and minutes from informal fact finding conferences, as well as conflict of interest letters.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged by the following accessions:
Minutes, 2011-2013 (51966).
Minutes, 2014-2015 (52208).
Minutes, 2016-2017 (52968).
Minutes, 2018-2020 (53634).
Contents List
- Minutes (all boards), 2011-2013 (Accession 51966)., Extent: 3 cubic feet (3 boxes). (Box 1-3)
  - Board for Professional and Occupational Regulation, 2011 Mar, June, Sept, Nov. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board for Professional and Occupational Regulation, 2012 Mar, Sept. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2011 Jan-Mar. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2011 Apr-June. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2011 July-Sept. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2011 Oct-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2012 Jan-Apr. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2012 May-Aug. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2012 Sept-Dec. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Board for Asbestos, Lead, Mold, and Home Inspectors, 2011. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board for Asbestos, Lead, Mold, and Home Inspectors, 2012 Jan-May. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Board for Asbestos, Lead, Mold, and Home Inspectors, 2012 Sept-Dec. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Auctioneers Board, 2011 June, July, Oct. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Auctioneers Board, 2011 Jan, Apr, Oct. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2011 Feb-May. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2011 June-July. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2011 Sept-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2012 Jan-Apr. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2012 May-Aug. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2012 Sept-Dec. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Board for Branch Pilots, 2011 Feb, June, July, Nov, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Board for Branch Pilots, 2012. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cemetery Board, 2011. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cemetery Board, 2012 Feb, May, Aug, Oct. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Common Interest Community Board, 2011 Mar, Apr, June, July, Sept-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Common Interest Community Board, 2012 Jan, Mar, Apr, May, June, Sept. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Board for Contractors, 2011 Jan-Feb. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Board for Contractors, 2011 Mar-Apr. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Board for Contractors, 2011 May-June. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Board for Contractors, 2011 July-Aug. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Board for Contractors, 2011 Sept-Nov. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Board for Contractors, 2011 Dec. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Board for Contractors, 2012 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Board for Contractors, 2012 Feb-Mar. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Board for Contractors, 2012 Apr. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Board for Contractors, 2012 May. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Board for Contractors, 2012 June. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Board for Contractors, 2012 July. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Board for Contractors, 2012 Aug-Sept. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Board for Contractors, 2012 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Board for Contractors, 2012 Nov-Dec. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Fair Housing Board, 2011. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Fair Housing Board, 2012. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Board for Geology, 2011 Jan, Apr, July, Oct. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Board for Geology, 2012 Jan, Mar, June. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Board for Hearing Aid Specialists, 2011 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Board for Hearing Aid Specialists, 2012 May, Dec. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Board for Opticians, 2011 Aug, Nov, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Board for Opticians, 2012 Mar, Apr. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Polygraph Examiners Advisory Board, 2011 Apr, May, July, Sept, Octg. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Professional Boxing, Wrestling, and Martial Arts Advisory Board, 2011 Mar, July, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Board for Professional Soil Scientists and Wetlands Professionals, 2011 Apr, July, Oct. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Board for Professional Soil Scientists and Wetlands Professionals, 2012 Jan, Apr. (Box 2, Folder 26a)
  - Board for Professional Soil Scientists, Wetlands Professionals and Geologists, 2012 Sept, Oct, Dec. (Box 2, Folder 26b)
  - Real Estate Board, 2011 Jan-Apr. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Real Estate Board, 2011 May-July. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Real Estate Board, 2011 Aug-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Real Estate Board, 2012 Jan-Feb. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Real Estate Board, 2012 Mar-Apr. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Real Estate Board, 2012 May-July. (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Real Estate Board, 2012 Sept-Oct. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Real Estate Board, 2012 Nov-Dec. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Real Estate Appraisers Board, 2011 Jan-June, Aug, Sept, Nov, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Real Estate Appraisers Board, 2012 Jan, Feb, May-Nov. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Board for Waste Management Facility Operators, 2011 May, June, Aug. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Board for Waste Management Facility Operators, 2012 Jan, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Board for Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage Professionals, 2011 Apr-July, Sept-Nov. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Board for Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage Professionals, 2012 Jan, Feb, May-July, Oct, Nov. (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Minutes (all boards), 2014-2015 (Accession 52208)., Extent: 1.35 cubic feet (2 boxes). (Box 1-2)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2014. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2015 Mar-July. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2015 Aug-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Board for Asbestos, Lead and Home Inspectors, 2014. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Board for Asbestos, Lead and Home Inspectors, 2015. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Auctioneers Board, 2014 Jan, Apr. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Auctioneers Board, 2015 Jan, July, Oct. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2014 Feb-Nov. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2014 Jan-Nov. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Boxing, Martial Arts and Professional Wrestling Advisory Board, 2015 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Board for Branch Pilots, 2014 Jan, July, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board for Branch Pilots, 2015 Jan, Apr, July, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Cemetery Board, 2014 Jan, June, July. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cemetery Board, 2015 Feb, June, Oct. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Common Interest Community Board, 2014 Mar, June, Sept, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Common Interest Community Board, 2015 Feb, Mar, June, Sept, Oct, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Board for Contractors, 2014 Mar, Apr. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board for Contractors, 2014 June, Aug. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board for Contractors, 2014 Oct, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Board for Contractors, 2015 Mar. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Board for Contractors, 2015 Apr. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Board for Contractors, 2015 June. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Board for Contractors, 2015 July. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Board for Contractors, 2015 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Board for Contractors, 2015 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Board for Contractors, 2015 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Fair Housing Board, 2014 Mar, June, Sept, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Fair Housing Board, 2015 Mar, June, Sept, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Board for Hearing Aid Specialists and Opticians, 2014 Aug, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Board for Hearing Aid Specialists and Opticians, 2015 Feb, June, Sept, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Polygraph Examiners Advisory Board, 2014 Apr, Oct. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Polygraph Examiners Advisory Board, 2015 Jan, Apr, Oct. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Board for Professional and Occupational Regulation, 2014 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Board for Professional and Occupational Regulation, 2015 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Board for Professional Soil Scientists, Wetlands Professionals and Geologists, 2014 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Board for Professional Soil Scientists, Wetlands Professionals and Geologists, 2015. (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Real Estate Board, 2014 Jan, Mar, May, July, Sept, Nov. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Real Estate Board, 2015 Jan, Mar, May. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Real Estate Appraisers Board, 2014 Feb, May, Aug, Nov. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Real Estate Appraisers Board, 2015 Feb, May, Aug, Oct, Nov. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Real Estate Appraisers Board, 2014 Feb, May, Aug, Nov. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Board for Waste Management Facility Operators, 2014 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Board for Waste Management Facility Operators, 2015 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Board for Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage Professionals, 2014 Jan, Apr, July, Sept, Oct, Nov. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Board for Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage Professionals, 2014 Jan, Mar, Apr, May, July, Oct, Nov. (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Minutes (all boards), 2016-2017 (Accession 52968)., Extent: 2 cubic feet (2 boxes). (Box 1-2)
  - Board for Professional and Occupational Regulation, 2016 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board for Professional and Occupational Regulation, 2017 Sept, Nov. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2016 Feb, Mar, May. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2016 June, Aug. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2016 Sept-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2017 Jan-Mar. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2017 Apr-Aug. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2017 Sept-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects (Section minutes), 2018 Mar, May. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board for Asbestos, Lead and Home Inspectors, 2016. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Board for Asbestos, Lead and Home Inspectors, 2017. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Auctioneers Board, 2016. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Auctioneers Board, 2017. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2016 Feb, May. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2016 Aug, Nov. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2017 Feb, Mar, May. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2017 June, Aug, Nov, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Boxing, Martial Arts and Professioal Wrestling Advisory Board, 2017 Dec. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Board for Branch Pilots, 2016. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Board for Branch Pilots, 2017. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Cemetery Board, 2016. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Cemetery Board, 2017 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Common Interest Community Board, 2016. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Common Interest Community Board, 2017. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Board for Contractors, 2016 Feb, Mar. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Board for Contractors, 2016 Apr, July. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Board for Contractors, 2016 Aug, Sept. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Board for Contractors, 2016 Nov, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Board for Contractors, 2017 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Board for Contractors, 2017 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Board for Contractors, 2017 June. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Board for Contractors, 2017 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Board for Contractors, 2017 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Board for Contractors, 2017 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Board for Contractors, 2017 Dec. (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Fair Housing Board, 2016. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Fair Housing Board, 2017. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Board for Hearing Aid Specialists and Opticians, 2016. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Board for Hearing Aid Specialists and Opticians, 2016. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Board for Professional Soil Scientists, Wetlands Professionals and Geologists, 2016. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Board for Professional Soil Scientists, Wetlands Professionals and Geologists, 2016. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate Board, 2016 Jan, Mar, May. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Real Estate Board, 2016 July, Sept, Oct, Nov. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Real Estate Board, 2017 Jan, Mar, May. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Real Estate Board, 2017 July, Sept, Nov. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Real Estate Appraisers Board, 2016. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Real Estate Appraisers Board, 2017. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Board for Waste Management Facility Operators, 2016 July. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Board for Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage Professionals, 2016. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Board for Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage Professionals, 2017. (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Minutes (all boards), 2018-2020 (Accession 53634)., Extent: 2 cubic feet (2 boxes). (Box 1-2)
  - Board for Professional and Occupational Regulation, 2018 Mar, Nov. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board for Professional and Occupational Regulation, 2019 Mar, Oct, Dec; 2020 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2018 Jan, Feb, June, July, Aug. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2018 Sept, Oct, Nov, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2019 Feb, Mar, June, July. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2019 Aug, Sept, Nov, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board for Architects, Professional Engineers, Land Surveyors, Certified Interior Designers and Landscape Architects, 2020 Feb, July, Sept. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board for Asbestos, Lead, and Home Inspectors, 2018 Feb, May, June, Aug. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board for Asbestos, Lead, and Home Inspectors, 2019 Feb, May, Aug, Nov. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board for Asbestos, Lead, and Home Inspectors, 2020 Feb, Aug, Nov. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Auctioneers Board, 2018 Jan, Apr, July, Oct. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Auctioneers Board, 2019 Jan, Oct; 2020 Oct. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2018 Feb, Mar, May. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2018 Aug, Nov. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2019 Jan, Mar, Apr, May, June. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2019 Sept, Nov, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2020 Jan, Mar. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Board for Barbers and Cosmetology, 2020 July, Sept, Nov. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Boxing, Martial Arts and Wrestling Advisory Board, 2018 Oct; 2019 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Board for Branch Pilots, 2018 Mar, June, Sept, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Board for Branch Pilots, 2019 Mar, June, Sept, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Board for Branch Pilots, 2020 Mar, June, Sept, Dec. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Cemetery Board, 2018 Feb, Sept. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Cemetery Board, 2019 Feb, Sept. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Cemetery Board, 2020 Feb, Sept. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Common Interest Community Board, 2018 Mar, June, Sept, Nov. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Common Interest Community Board, 2019 Mar, June, Sept, Nov. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Common Interest Community Board, 2020 Mar, June, Sept. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Board for Contractors, 2018 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Board for Contractors, 2018 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Board for Contractors, 2018 June. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Board for Contractors, 2018 July. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Board for Contractors, 2018 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Board for Contractors, 2018 Oct. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Board for Contractors, 2018 Dec. (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Board for Contractors, 2019 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Board for Contractors, 2019 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Board for Contractors, 2019 June. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Board for Contractors, 2019 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Board for Contractors, 2019 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Board for Contractors, 2019 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Board for Contractors, 2019 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Board for Contractors, 2020 June. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Board for Contractors, 2020 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Board for Contractors, 2020 Sept. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Board for Contractors, 2020 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Board for Contractors, 2020 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Fair Housing Board, 2018 Mar, June, Aug, Dec. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Fair Housing Board, 2019 Mar, June, Aug, Dec. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Fair Housing Board, 2020 Mar, Aug. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Board for Hearing Aid Specialists and Opticians, 2018 Feb, Apr, June, July, Aug. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Board for Hearing Aid Specialists and Opticians, 2020 Aug, Oct. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Polygraph Examiners Advisory Board, 2019 Apr, July, Octg. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Board for Professional Soil Scientists, Wetlands Professionals, and Geologists, 2018 June, Sept, Dec. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Board for Professional Soil Scientists, Wetlands Professionals, and Geologists, 2019 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Real Estate Board, 2018 Jan, Feb, Mar, May. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Real Estate Board, 2018 June, July, Sept, Nov. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Real Estate Board, 2019 Jan, Apr, May. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Real Estate Board, 2019 July, Sept, Nov. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Real Estate Board, 2020 Jan, July, Sept, Nov. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Real Estate Appraisers Board, 2018 Feb, May, July, Oct, Nov. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Real Estate Appraisers Board, 2019 Feb, May, July, Oct. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Real Estate Appraisers Board, 2020 Jan, Feb, June, Oct. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Board for Waste Management Facility Operators, 2018 Apr. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Board for Waste Management Facility Operators, 2019 Apr, June, Dec. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Board for Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage Professionals, 2018 Jan, Apr, July, Oct. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Board for Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage Professionals, 2019 Jan, Apr, July, Oct. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Board for Waterworks and Wastewater Works Operators and Onsite Sewage Professionals, 2020 Jan, July, Oct. (Box 2, Folder 28)